var biologydata = {
  "total_size": 4,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question":
          "Who was the first scientist to coin the term SMOG and to describe the layers of SMOG?",
      "option1": "Nikola Tesla",
      "option2": " Stephen Hawking",
      "option3": "Dr Henry Antoine",
      "option4": "Nicolaus Copernicus",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The major photochemical smog is?",
      "option1": "Hydrogen peroxide",
      "option2": "Chlorofluorocarbon",
      "option3": "Peroxyacetyl nitrate",
      "option4": "All of the above",
      "ans": "b",
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "DDT and Aluminium cans are examples of",
      "option1": "Primary Pollutants",
      "option2": "Secondary pollutants",
      "option3": "Biodegradable Pollutants",
      "option4": "Non-Biodegradable",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Increased levels of air pollution results in ?",
      "option1": "Soil erosion",
      "option2": "Global warming",
      "option3": "Respiratory problems",
      "option4": "All of the above",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which of the following produces citric acid?",
      "option1": "Aspergillus",
      "option2": "Pseudomonas",
      "option3": "Saccharomyces",
      "option4": " Clostridium",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question":
          "Which of the following microorganisms is not used as a biofertilizer?",
      "option1": "Rhizobium",
      "option2": "Nostoc",
      "option3": "Mycorrhiza",
      "option4": "Agrobacterium",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question":
          "Which of the following organisms is used in alcoholic fermentation?",
      "option1": "Pseudomonas",
      "option2": "Aspergillus",
      "option3": "Saccharomyces",
      "option4": "Penicillium",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question":
          "A common biopesticide for preventing plants from butterfly caterpillars is ?",
      "option1": "Trichoderma",
      "option2": "Baculovirus",
      "option3": "Glomus",
      "option4": "Bacillus thuringiensis",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Yeast is used for the production of?",
      "option1": "Tetracycline",
      "option2": "Butanol",
      "option3": "Ethanol",
      "option4": "Citric Acid",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question":
          "Which of the following is used as a biofertilizer for soyabean crop?",
      "option1": "Rhizobium",
      "option2": "Azotobacter",
      "option3": "Nostoc",
      "option4": " Azospirillum",
      "ans": "a",
    },
  ]
};
